Guide to the Clark E. Warburton papers, 1920-1979
George Mason University Libraries
- Clark Warburton Papers
  - Assets, Liabilities and Capital Accounts- Report of Call Nos.55-56. 4-12-61, 6-30-61 (Folder 24, Box 38)
  - Assets, Liabilities and Capital Accounts- Report of Call Nos.57-58. 9-27-61, 12-30-61 (Folder 25, Box 38)
  - Assets, Liabilities and Capital Accounts- Report of Call Nos.59-60. 3-26-62, 6-30-62 (Folder 26, Box 38)
  - Assets, Liabilities and Capital Accounts- Report of Call Nos.61-62. 9-28-62, 12-28-62 (Folder 27, Box 38)
  - Assets, Liabilities and Capital Accounts-Report of Call No.66. 12-20-63 (Folder 28, Box 38)
  - Assets, Liabilities and Capital Accounts- Report of Call No.68. 6-30-64 (Folder 29, Box 38)
  - FDIC- Assets and liabilities of all insured banks. 10-8-64 (Folder 30, Box 38)
  - Assets, Liabilities and Capital Accounts-Report of Call No.70. 12-31-64 (Folder 31, Box 38)
  - FDIC Report, Nos.32-46. 12-31-56 through 12-31-59. (Folder 1-15, Box 39)
  - Assets and liabilities(commercial and mutual savings banks). 6-30-70 (Folder 1, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities(commercial and mutual savings banks). 6-30-69 (Folder 2, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities(commercial and mutual savings banks). 12-31-69 (Folder 3, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Total U.S. 6-29-63 (Folder 4, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Total other areas. 6-29-63 (Folder 5, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Total U.S. and others. 6-29-63 (Folder 6, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Total U.S. 12-28-62 (Folder 7, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Total other areas. 12-28-62 (Folder 8, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Total U.S. and others. 12-28-62 (Folder 9, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Total U.S. 6-30-62 (Folder 10, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Total other areas. 6-30-62 (Folder 11, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Total U.S. and others. 6-30-62 (Folder 12, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Total U.S. and other areas. 12-30-61 (Folder 13, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Total other areas. 12-30-61 (Folder 14, Box 40)
  - Liabilities and capital accounts- 50 states and D.C. 12-30-61 (Folder 15, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Total other areas. 6-30-61 (Folder 16, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Total U.S. 6-30-61 (Folder 17, Box 40)
  - Liabilities and capital accounts-Total U.S. 6-30-61 (Folder 18, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Total other areas. 12-31-60 (Folder 19, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- 48 states and D.C. 12-31-60 (Folder 20, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- 50 states and D.C. 12-31-60 (Folder 21, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Total U.S. 12-31-60 (Folder 22, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Total U.S. 6-15-60 (Folder 23, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- 50 states and D.C. 6-15-60 (Folder 24, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- 48 states and D.C. 6-15-60 (Folder 25, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Total other areas. 6-15-60 (Folder 26, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Total other areas. 12-31-59 (Folder 27, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Total U.S. 12-31-59 (Folder 28, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- 50 states and D.C. 12-31-59 (Folder 29, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- 48 states and D.C. 12-31-59 (Folder 30, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- 48 states and D.C. 6-10-59 (Folder 31, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- 50 states and D.C. 6-19-59 (Folder 32, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Total U.S. 6-10-59 (Folder 33, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Total other areas. 6-10-59 (Folder 34, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. 12-31-58 (Folder 35, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental other areas. 12-31-58 (Folder 36, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. and other areas. 12-31-58 (Folder 37, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. and other areas. 6-23-58 (Folder 38, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental other areas. 6-23-58 (Folder 39, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. 6-23-58 (Folder 40, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. and other areas. 12-31-57 (Folder 41, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. 12-31-57 (Folder 42, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental other areas. 12-31-57 (Folder 43, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental other areas. 6-06-57 (Folder 44, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. 6-06-57 (Folder 45, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. and other areas. 6-06-57 (Folder 46, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. and other areas. 12-31-56 (Folder 47, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. 12-31-56 (Folder 48, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental other areas. 12-31-56 (Folder 49, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental other areas. 6-30-56 (Folder 50, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. and other areas. 6-30-56 (Folder 51, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. 6-30-56 (Folder 52, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. 12-31-55 (Folder 53, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental other areas. 12-31-55 (Folder 54, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. and other areas. 12-31-55 (Folder 55, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. 6-30-55 (Folder 56, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental other areas. 6-30-55 (Folder 57, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. and other areas. 6-30-55 (Folder 58, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. 12-31-54 (Folder 59, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental other areas. 12-31-54 (Folder 60, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. and other areas. 12-31-54 (Folder 61, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. 6-30-54 (Folder 62, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental other areas. 6-30-54 (Folder 63, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. and other areas. 6-30-54 (Folder 64, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. 12-31-53 (Folder 65, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental other areas. 12-31-53 (Folder 66, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. and other areas. 12-31-53 (Folder 67, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. 6-30-53 (Folder 68, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental other areas. 6-30-53 (Folder 69, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. and other areas. 6-30-53 (Folder 70, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Possessions. 12-31-52 (Folder 71, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. and possessions. 12-31-52 (Folder 72, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Possessions. 6-30-52 (Folder 73, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. and possessions. 6-30-52 (Folder 74, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Possessions. 12-31-51 (Folder 75, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. 12-31-51 (Folder 76, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. and possessions. 12-31-51 (Folder 77, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Possessions. 12-30-50 (Folder 78, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Possessions. 6-30-50 (Folder 79, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Possessions and total. 12-31-49 (Folder 80, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. and possessions. 12-31-49 (Folder 81, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Possessions and total. 6-30-49 (Folder 82, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. and possessions. 6-30-49 (Folder 83, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. 12-31-48 (Folder 84, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Possessions and total. 12-31-48 (Folder 85, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. and possessions. 12-31-48 (Folder 86, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. 6-30-48 (Folder 87, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Possessions and total. 6-30-48 (Folder 88, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. and possessions. 6-30-48 (Folder 89, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. 12-31-47 (Folder 90, Box 40)
  - Assets and liabilities- Continental U.S. and possessions. 12-31-47 (Folder 91, Box 40)
  - Call Report- FED member banks, 1936-47. (Folder 1, Box 41)
  - FED pamphlets and publications- Monetary policy. (Folder 2, Box 41)
  - FED Call Report. (Folder 3, Box 41)
  - Reports on audit of the corporation. (Folder 4, Box 41)
  - Improving the Monetary Aggregates, Staff Economic Studies(Board of Governors of the FED), Absorption of Exchange Changes by Leo T. Crowley, The payment of Interest on Money and The Prohibition of Interest on Demand Deposits by Richard E. Towey, and Economic Research Unit by Neil B. Murphy. (Box 42)
  - FED Pamphlets- Supervision Reserves Collection. (Folder 1, Box 42)
  - FED Pamphlets- Banking Structure Suspensions. (Folder 2, Box 42)
  - FED Pamphlets- Distribution of Deposits and Cash Balances. (Folder 3, Box 42)
  - Staff Economic Studies- "Effects of Money on Interest Rates" by William E. Gibson, "A Technique for Forecasting Defense Expenditures" by Harvey Galper and Edward Gramlich, "The Regulation of Short -Term capital Movements: Western European Techniques in the 1960s" by Rodney H. Mills, Jr., and "A Disaggregated Model of the U.S. Balance of Trade" by William H. Branson. (Box 43)
  - Staff Economic Studies- "The Labor Market and Potential Output of the Federal Reserve-MIT Econometric Model: A Preliminary Report" by A.J. Tella and P.A. Tinsley, "The Lags Between Investment Decisions and Their Causes" by Shirley Almon, and "A Test of the Deposit Relationship Hypothesis" by Neil B. Murphy. (Box 43)
  - Staff Economic Studies- "Interest Rates and the Demand for Consumer Durable Goods" by Michael J. Hamburger, and "Measures of Industrial Production and Final Demand" by Clayton Gehman and Cornelia Motheral. (Box 43)
  - "Defining the Money Supply." (Folder 1, Box 43)
  - FED Papers: See list. (Folder 2, Box 43)
  - Monetary aggregates and money market conditions. (Folder 3, Box 43)
  - New England Economic Review- FED Bank of Boston. (Folder 4, Box 43)
  - Numerical specifications of financial variables and their role in monetary policy. (Folder 5, Box 43)
  - Open market operations in 1973. (Folder 6, Box 43)
  - Recent regulatory changes in reserve requirements and check collection. (Folder 7, Box 43)
  - Staff Economic Study- Channels of Monetary Policy. (Folder 8, Box 43)
  - Some Essentials of International Monetary Reform. (Folder 9, Box 43)
  - Some Problems of Central Banking. (Folder 10, Box 43)
  - Letters to college classes in Banking and Economics. (Folder 1, Box 44)
  - Financial lessons of 1974. (Folder 1, Box 45)
  - "Financial Prospects", 1975. (Folder 2, Box 45)
  - "Inflation and the Federal Reserve." (Folder 3, Box 45)
  - "International Monetary Situation." (Folder 4, Box 45)
  - "Oil and Finance- Public Policy for the Economy." (Folder 5, Box 45)
  - Statements by Arthur F. Burns- Chairman, Board of Governors of the Federal Reserve (1). (Folder 6, Box 45)
  - Statements by Arthur F. Burns- Chairman, Board of Governors of the Federal Reserve System (2). (Folder 7, Box 45)
  - "What should we do about worldwide and domestic inflation?" (Folder 8, Box 45)
  - Administrative inflation and public policy. (Folder 1, Box 46)
  - A proposed method of estimating deposits at all banks in the U.S. (Folder 2, Box 46)
  - Committee on Techniques of Statistical Analysis. (Folder 3, Box 46)
  - Definitions, Interest Rates and the Relevance of Money Substitutes. (Folder 4, Box 46)
  - General Motors-Business Barometers. (Folder 5, Box 46)
  - IMF Papers on National Income Accounts. (Folder 6, Box 46)
  - Deposit Insurance Coverage-FDIC Position. (Folder 7, Box 46)
  - Material From Committee on Financial Institutions. (Folder 8, Box 46)
  - Prohibition of Interest on Demand Deposits. (Folder 9, Box 46)
  - Report to the Temporary National Economic Committee- Money, Savings, Durable Goods, Consumer Goods by Currie, Terborgh, and Basie. (Folder 10, Box 46)
  - British Government Securities in the 20th Century. (Folder 1, Box 47)
  - How Variable is the Velocity of Money? (Folder 2, Box 47)
  - IMF-Money and Banking Manual. (Folder 3, Box 47)
  - The Sterling Crisis of 1337-1339. (Folder 4, Box 47)
  - Tobin- Monetary Theory Manuscript (1). (Folder 5, Box 47)
  - Tobin- Monetary Theory Manuscript (2). (Folder 6, Box 47)
  - Tobin- Monetary Theory Manuscript (3). (Folder 7, Box 47)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Department of Economics Working Papers- No.16, No.18, No. 21, August, 1968 and No. 35R, No.48, August, 1969. (Box 48)
  - GNP Data Improvement Project Report. (Box 48)
  - Comment by D.J. Daly on Monetary Policy and Consumer Expenditures: The Historical Evidence by Meiselman and Simpson. (Folder 1, Box 48)
  - Excerpt from Political Discourses by David Hume. (Folder 2, Box 48)
  - Integration and Indexation- A Seminar Sponsored by the Tax Foundation, Inc. (Folder 3, Box 48)
  - Interest Rates and Price Level Changes, 1952-1969. (Folder 4, Box 48)
  - James Mill and India's Economic Development. (Folder 5, Box 48)
  - "Money is Everything" Economics- A Tempest in a Teapot by Wilfred Lewis, Jr. (Folder 6, Box 48)
  - Shadow European Economic Policy Committee. (Folder 7, Box 48)
  - The Irreconcilable Difference Between R.G. Hawtrey and J.M. Keynes. (Folder 8, Box 48)
  - Business Income Study Group. (Folder 1, Box 49)
  - Papers From Business Income Study Group (1). (Folder 2, Box 49)
  - Papers From Business Income Study Group (2). (Folder 3, Box 49)
  - United States of America Monetary and Economic Situation, 1951-1960. (Box 49)
  - Recent Economic History of Five Towns by Dorothy C. Bacon. (Box 49)
  - Report of the Study Group on the Creation of Reserve Assets. 31-5-65 (Box 49)
  - Morals, Computers, and the Philosophy of Man by Peter Warburton. (Box 50)
  - Monetary Control and the Distribution of Money by William G. Dewald. (Box 50)
  - Michael, George- Dissertation, with letter to Dr. Warburton and reply. (Folder 1, Box 50)
  - Institute for Economic Analysis- Charts and Special Reports. (Folder 2, Box 50)
  - Shadow Open Market Committee- 1st, 2nd, and 3rd meetings. (Folder 3, Box 50)
  - Shadow Open Market Committee- 4th meeting. (Folder 4, Box 50)
  - Shadow Open Market Committee- 5th meeting. (Folder 5, Box 50)
  - Shadow Open Market Committee- 6th meeting. (Folder 6, Box 50)
  - Shadow Open Market Committee- 7th meeting. (Folder 7, Box 50)
  - Shadow Open Market Committee- 8th meeting. (Folder 8, Box 50)
  - The Life of John Birch by H. W. Welch, Jr. (Box 51)
  - U.S. Department of Commerce- A Social Economic Grouping of the Gainful Workers of the United States 1930. (Box 51)
  - Branch Banking and the Structure of Competition. (Folder 1, Box 51)
  - "Improving Monetary Aggregates"- collection of articles. (Folder 2, Box 51)
  - The Gold Situation (Folder 3, Box 51)
  - Thesis- John Pilgrim (1). (Folder 1, Box 52)
  - Thesis- John Pilgrim (2). (Folder 2, Box 52)
  - Christensen, L. R. and Dale W. Jorgenson."U.S. Income, Saving, and Wealth, 1929-1969." Harvard Institute of Economic Research, Discussion Paper Series, December 1972. (Box 52)
  - Christensen L.R. and Dale W. Jorgenson. " Measuring the Performance of the Private Sector of the U.S. Economy, 1929-1969." Harvard Institute of Economic Research, Discussion Paper Series, December 1972. (Box 52)
  - Linkages Between Monetary Policy and the General Economy: A Framework for Research- Report of the Ad Hoc Committee on Monetary Research Projects. (Box 52)
  - Burger, Albert E. and Leonall Anderson. "The Development of Explanatory Economic Hypotheses for Monetary Management." Federal Reserve Bank of St. Louis, November 8, 1968,Working Paper No.5. (Box 52)
  - Economic Abstracts, Nos.1 through 22, April 1952-May 1956. (Folder 1-20, Box 53)
  - Essays in International Finance, Nos. 36, 39, 41, 42, 46, 47, 51, 52, 53, and 54, March 1961- May 1966. (Folder 1-10, Box 54)
  - Special Papers in International Economics, Nos.3-4, August 1962- April 1963. (Folder 11-12, Box 54)
  - Reprints in International Finance, No.13, March 1970. (Folder 13, Box 54)
  - Princeton Studies in International Finance, No.10, 1963. (Folder 14, Box 54)
  - Statistical Supplement, 1947. (Folder 15, Box 54)
  - U.S. Income and Output. (Folder 16, Box 54)
  - Survey of Current Business, 1936, 1938, March 1938, April 1943, July 1960, July 1962, and February 1963. (Folder 17-21, Box 54)
  - Income Distribution in the U.S. (Folder 22, Box 54)
  - Survey of Current Business, 1936, 1938, March 1938, April 1943, July 1960, July 1962, and February 1963. (Folder 23-24, Box 54)
  - A.B.A Economic Policy Commission, Monetary Study Nos.1-6. (Folder 1a, Box 55)
  - Assets of Reserve City Bankers. (Folder 1b, Box 55)
  - Articles from The People Money, June 1935-April 1937. (Folder 2, Box 55)
  - American Economists Council. (Folder 3, Box 55)
  - Current Trends in Banking and Business. (Folder 4, Box 55)
  - Publications of IMF. (Folder 5, Box 55)
  - The Banker (Folder 6, Box 55)
  - Index- South African Journal of Economics. (Folder 1, Box 56)
  - Index- Essays in International Finance. (Folder 2, Box 56)
  - Treasury Department. (Folder 3, Box 56)
  - Subject Index of Bulletins Published by the Bureau of Labor Statistics, 1915-59. (Box 56)
  - Techniques of Preparing Major BLS Statistical Series. (Box 56)
  - Enterprise and Social Progress, 1916. (Folder 1, Box 57)
  - Silver in America. (Folder 2, Box 57)
  - Report of the President's Committee. (Folder 3, Box 57)
  - Consumer Incomes in the U.S., August 1938. (Folder 4, Box 57)
  - Economic and Social Problems, January 1935. (Folder 5, Box 57)
  - Banking's Reference- Supplement, March 1933. (Folder 6, Box 57)
  - Savings Bank Journal, November 1935. (Folder 7, Box 57)
  - The balance of international payments of the U.S. in 1929. (Folder 8, Box 57)
  - American direct investments in foreign, 1936. (Folder 9, Box 57)
  - Foreign investments in the United States. (Folder 10, Box 57)
  - Long-term debts in the United States. (Folder 11, Box 57)
  - Banking after the crises. (Folder 12, Box 57)
  - Journals on Wartime Financing- Bibliography. (Folder 1, Box 58)
  - Wartime Financing, 1940-1950. (Folder 2-10, Box 58)
  - Readings, 1950, 1952, 1953, 1954, 1956, 1957, and 1961. (Folder 1-7, Box 59)
  - The Exact Science of Economics. (Folder 1, Box 60)
  - Journal of Economic Abstracts, January 1963. (Folder 2, Box 60)
  - Economic Growth and Monetary Stability, November 1964. (Folder 3, Box 60)
  - Retrospection, December 1964. (Folder 4, Box 60)
  - Factionalism in the Social Sciences, February 1964. (Folder 5, Box 60)
  - Time Deposit Growth and the Employment of Bank Funds. (Folder 6, Box 60)
  - The World's Money. (Folder 7, Box 60)
  - Business Review, June, March 1965. (Folder 8, Box 60)
  - Monthly Review, December 1970. (Folder 9, Box 60)
  - Yeager, Leland B. "Monetary Policy and Economic Performance." (Folder 10, Box 60)
  - National Bureau Report, May 1973. (Folder 11, Box 60)
  - Economic Prospects, Summer 1973. (Folder 12, Box 60)
  - Articles and data regarding stock of money. (Folder 1, Box 61)
  - Data regarding capital goods review. (Folder 2, Box 61)
  - Federal Reserve System: Current Policy, 1960s. (Folder 3, Box 61)
  - Federal Reserve System- Structure, Power, and Reserve Requirements. (Folder 4, Box 61)
  - Income Velocity. (Folder 5, Box 61)
  - FR Bank of St. Louis- Monetary base, 1877 revision. (Folder 6, Box 61)
  - Monetary Policy. (Folder 7, Box 61)
  - NBER- Inflation Cronology. (Folder 8, Box 61)
  - Velocity- U.S. and U.K. from Anna Schwartz. (Folder 9, Box 61)
  - Migration Materials. (Folder 10, Box 61)
  - The Chase Economic Bulletin. 12-15-20, 2-28-21, 5-20-21, 1-12-22, 5-6-22, 7-23-22, 8-31-22, 11-11-22, 9-29-30, 11-10-32. (Folder 1-10, Box 62)
  - NBER Bulletin, Nos. 44, 46-63, 65-68, 70-78. 1-27-33, 5-1-33, 6-30-33, 10-31-33, 1-26-34, 7-7-34, 4-18-34, 6-28-34, 11-15-34, 12-22-34, 3-15-34, 5-11-34, 5-10-35, 7-1-35, 11-15-35, 6-15-36, 11-9-36, 12-7-36, 12-21-36, 9-15-37, 11-29-37, 12-27-37, 9-25-38, 11-27-38, 2-5-39, 6-25-39, 9-17-39, 10-15-39, 4-28-40. (Folder 11-41, Box 62)
  - News Bulletin, No.43. 9-19-32 (Folder 42, Box 62)
  - Recovery With Inflation, 1976. (Folder 43, Box 62)
  - Five-year Budget Projections, December 1976 and April 1977. (Folder 44-45, Box 62)
  - The President's Fiscal Year 1978. (Folder 46, Box 62)
  - Budget Issue Paper(International Financial), March 1977. (Folder 47, Box 62)
  - The Disappointing Recovery. 1-11-77 (Folder 48, Box 62)
  - Inflation and Unemployment. 6-30-75 (Folder 49, Box 62)
  - Sustaining a Balanced Expansion. 8-3-76 (Folder 50, Box 62)
  - Recovery: How Fast and How Far? 9-17-75 (Folder 51, Box 62)
  - Budget Options For Fiscal Year 1978. (Folder 52, Box 62)
  - The Chase Economic Bulletin, Nos.1-5. 3-27-23, 4-27-23, 8-10-23, 10-4-23, 11-19-23. (Folder 1-5, Box 63)
  - The Chase Economic Bulletin, Nos. 1-5. 4-28-24, 5-5-24, 8-4-24, 10-9-24, 10-23-24. (Folder 6, 7, 38, 39, 40, Box 63)
  - The Chase Economic Bulletin, Nos. 1-3. 3-23-25, 6-10-25, 8-24-25 (Folder 10, 11, 49, Box 63)
  - The Chase Economic Bulletin, Nos. 1-3. 4-2-26, 6-21-26, 11-8-26 (Folder 8, 9, 12, Box 63)
  - The Chase Economic Bulletin, Nos. 1-4. 2-18-27, 4-8-27, 6-21-27, 10-29-27 (Folder 13-16, Box 63)
  - The Chase Economic Bulletin, Nos. 1-4. 6-4-28, 6-25-29, 9-27-28, 10-31-28 (Folder 31-34, Box 63)
  - The Chase Economic Bulletin, Nos. 1-6. 2-11-29, 2-13-29, 5-8-29, 7-20-29, 10-12-29, 11-22-29 (Folder 25-30, Box 63)
  - The Chase Economic Bulletin, Nos. 1-2. 3-14-30, 5-8-30 (Folder 24, 35, Box 63)
  - The Chase Economic Bulletin, Nos. 1-5. 3-16-31, 3-23-31, 6-12-31, 10-8-31, 11-20-31 (Folder 20-23 and 36, Box 63)
  - The Chase Economic Bulletin, Nos. 1, 2, 4, 5. 4-25-32, 5-16-32, 11-17-32, 12-12-32 (Folder 18, 19, 37, 48, Box 63)
  - The Chase Economic Bulletin, Nos. 1-4. 5-6-33, 5-9-33, 6-9-33, 12-13-33 (Folder 44-47, Box 63)
  - The Chase Economic Bulletin, No. 1. 5-1-34 (Folder 43, Box 63)
  - The Chase Economic Bulletin, Nos.41-42. 1-26-37, 4-13-37 (Folder 41, 42, Box 63)
  - The Income of the American People and the Ratio of Foreign to Domestic Trade 1890-1924. (Folder 50, Box 63)
  - Critiques of Peter Temin. (Folder 1, Box 64)
  - Federal Deposit Insurance Reform. (Folder 2, Box 64)
  - Money Supply (1). (Folder 3, Box 64)
  - Money Supply (2). (Folder 4, Box 64)
  - Articles by David Fand. (Folder 1-3, Box 65)
  - Economic Indicators, the Federal Reserve, and Monetary Policy. (Folder 4-6, Box 65)
  - Articles on Monetary Systems. (Folder 1, Box 66)
  - Economic Indicators and Monetary Policy. (Folder 2, 3, Box 66)
  - Foreign Language Reprints. (Folder 4, Box 66)
  - Lagged Reserves. (Folder 5, Box 66)
  - Laffer and Canterbery- Economic Indicators and Monetary Policy. (Folder 6, Box 66)
  - Monetary Policy. (Folder 7, Box 66)
  - 1910-1920, 1930, 1940, 1950, 1960, 1970. (Folder 1-6, Box 67)
  - The Economist, "The Age of Inflation", 1950. (Folder 7, Box 67)
  - AFL- CIO- Relationship of Prices to Economic Stability and Growth. (Folder 1, Box 68)
  - Aldrich, Nelson W. (Folder 2, Box 68)
  - Anderson, Benjamin, Jr. (Folder 3, Box 68)
  - Anderson, Clay J. (Folder 4, Box 68)
  - Ando, Albert K. (Folder 5, Box 68)
  - Angell, Cames W. (Folder 6, Box 68)
  - Aschheim, Joseph (Folder 7, Box 68)
  - Bassie, Lewis V. (Folder 8, Box 68)
  - Beem, Eugene R. (Folder 9, Box 68)
  - Bell, James W. (Folder 10, Box 68)
  - Benner, Calude L. (Folder 11, Box 68)
  - Berle, A. A. (Folder 12, Box 68)
  - Berridge, William A. (Folder 13, Box 68)
  - Bratt, Elmer C. (Folder 14, Box 68)
  - Brown, E. H. Phelps (Folder 15, Box 68)
  - Brown, Harry G. (Folder 16, Box 68)
  - Buchanan, James M. (Folder 17, Box 68)
  - Burgess, Randolph W. (Folder 18, Box 68)
  - Burns, Arthur F. (Folder 19, Box 68)